spiderofficechairs.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy & Security**

We recognize the trust you place in us to safeguard your privacy. Hence we emphasize the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. We welcome your questions and feedback about our Privacy Policy or our privacy commitments, and invite you to [Contact Us](https://cvshealth.com/contact).

**Note:**   
Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.

By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

**Privacy Policy and Consent**

This privacy policy lets you know what information we collect, how we may share that information, and your choices regarding the sharing of your information. This policy applies to VistaStores.com, any VistaStores Affiliate sites where you may interact with any of the VistaStores Family of Companies, and other places where we may collect personal information.

**Information Collected By Automated Means:** ****

Personally Identifiable Information: Is information we collect that uniquely identifies you, the customer. This information may contain name, shipping address, email address, phone number, and prescription information, as well as other information you may choose to share while interacting with our site and online services.

Non-Personal Information: Anonymous information is that information we collect that is not traceable to any individual person or computer. VistaStores utilizes this data to analyze trends and understand customer needs while shopping and interacting on our site so that we can provide a better user experience. For example, VistaStores may use cookies, web beacons, log files and other technologies to collect information about visitors to our Website, and interactions with our online advertisements and offerings.

### Information We Collect

**Contact Information**

we may collect the names and user names of our customers and other visitors. Additionally, we may collect your purchase history, billing and shipping addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and other digital contact information. We may also collect information that you provide us about others.

**Returns Information**

when you return a product to our stores or request a refund or exchange, you may be asked to provide your name, address, phone number and information that identifies you, such as your driver’s license. We use the information we collect from you and capture off of your government issued ID to process and track returns and to help detect and prevent fraud and otherwise administer our loss prevention program. To learn more about our Returns Policy, [click here](http://www.homedepot.com/c/Return_Policy).

**Demographic Information**  
**  
** We may collect information about products or services you like, reviews you submit, or where you shop. We might also collect information like your age or gender.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our Website.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or  
income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

**Links**

Our websites contain links to third party websites. If you click on one of those links, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This Privacy and Security Statement does not apply to the information practices of those websites. You should read the privacy policies of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for third party websites.

**Third Party Features**

The Service also may include an activity feed, social media buttons and widgets, such as the Facebook "Like" button or the "Share This" button. These features may collect and display your Personal Information, your IP address and the page you are visiting on the Service and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. These features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Service and your interactions with them are governed by the privacy policy of the third party that provides the feature.

**Use of Service via Mobile Device**

If you use the Service through your mobile device, we may collect your geo-location information to assist us in fulfilling your order. We will not share this information with third parties and will only use this information for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order. You may at any time prevent the Service from using your location by turning this option off at the device level.

When you use the Service through your mobile device, we also collect device type and UUID; a unique identifier generated within the App, and stores this information in log files. We use this information to provide you with the most up to date application and features, or to advertise or promote products or services to you that are applicable to your device type.

**How Your Personal Information Is Used, Processed and Disclosed**

Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, VistaStores does not rent, sell, trade or disclose your Personal Information to third parties without your prior consent. VistaStores may, however, use, process and disclose Personal Information to:

  1. Send information to customers about orders;
    1. Fulfill your orders;
    2. Process and collect your payments;
    3. Administer "VistaStores Rewards" and other customer loyalty programs;
    4. Send you promotional marketing material about VistaStores company and partners;
    5. Produce content for our activity feed feature;
    6. Customize, analyze, adjust and improve the Service to better meet your needs;
    7. Execute a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion;
    8. Enforce VistaStores agreements with you;

10\. Provide you with important administrative information regarding the Service, such as changes to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, rewards and loyalty programs and other policies;

11\. Prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities; and

12\. Comply with potential requests of law enforcement or data protection agencies.

**Third Party Service Providers**

VistaStores employs other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, serving ads on our behalf, providing search results and links, and processing credit card payments. These third-party service providers have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but may not use it for any other purpose.

**Acquisition of VistaStores**

Information about customers is considered an asset of VistaStores and, as such, may be transferred to another company as part of a merger or acquisition.

**Information Sharing For Marketing Purposes**

To provide you with information about products and services that may be useful to you, we may partner with select reputable organizations whose privacy policies we believe are consistent with ours. Such organizations may include other retailers and magazine publishers. Through these arrangements, we may share, exchange, cross-reference and/or rent your name and mailing address.

If you do not want us to share your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes, please contact us [here.](https://www.dwellstudio.com/help/faq.php) Immediately after your request has been processed, your information will no longer be shared with any third party for marketing purposes.

**Retention of Personal Information**

VistaStores retains Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law.

**Accessing and updating your personal information and preferences**

**Modifying or deleting your personal information**

If you would like to modify or delete your Personal Information, please contact us [here](https://www.dwellstudio.com/help/faq.php) with clear instructions about what you would like to be modified or deleted. We will respond to your request promptly.

**Changing Your Subscription Preferences**

If you tell us that you do not want us to use your Personal Information to contact you, VistaStores will respect your wishes. If you are a registered user, you may change your preferences to receive or not to receive email or other communications from us by logging in to your account and indicating those preferences on the "My Account" section of our Service.

You may also instruct VistaStores to stop sending you emails, newsletters or other information by following the ‘unsubscribe’ instructions provided in the email. VistaStores may, however, continue to use your Personal Information to contact you to service your account or as otherwise authorized by law. Please note that if you use more than one name or e-mail address when communicating with VistaStores or using the Service, you may continue to receive communications from VistaStores to any name and/or email address not specified in your opt-out request.

**Information for visitors from California and outside of the United States**

**California residents**

California law permits individuals who provide VistaStores with Personal Information and who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To request this information, please contact us [here.](https://www.dwellstudio.com/help/faq.php)

**Visitors From Outside Of the United States**

The Service is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting the Service from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable US laws. Please note that data protection and other applicable laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those laws or regulations in your country or may otherwise differ from the data protection or consumer protection laws in your country. By using the Service, you consent to transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Security Precautions**

Our Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. When we post modifications to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this web page. The modified Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting on the Service. Your continued use of the Service after the posting of the modified Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to abide and be bound by it. If we make any material change, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Service prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you object to any modification, your sole recourse is to stop using the Service.

**Tell us what you think**  
If you have any comments or questions about VistaStores privacy statement, please e-mail us at [info[@]VistaStores.com](mailto:info@VistaStores.com "info@VistaStores.com")
